<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.AliveGR" name="AliveGR" version="1.31.1" provider-name="Twilight0">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.alivegr.artwork" version="3.0.3"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.alivegr.logos" version="1.0.2"/>
        <import addon="script.module.youtube.dl" version="18.619.0" optional="true"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.0.31"/>
        <import addon="script.module.streamlink.base" version="2019.06.23"/>
        <import addon="script.module.tulip" version="2.3.8"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.4.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.pyxbmct" version="1.2.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video audio image executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">AliveGR, Kodi media center addon</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">AliveGR is an addon allowing streaming content available mostly in Greek language.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">AliveGR's author does not host, stream or distribute any of the content displayed inside this software and cannot be held responsible for the quality or availability of the listed streams.
On demand content is scraped from various websites and is freely available on the internet on public domains. This software acts only as a search engine.
Kindly note that AliveGR is not an official part of the media player you are running, and therefore not to be mentioned within official support channels, this addon has nothing to do with the media player itself, nor it’s intended use, it is simply a third party plugin which has been added to your system and it is provided "as is" with no warranty.</disclaimer>
        <summary lang="el_GR">AliveGR, Μικροεφαρμογή κέντρου πολυμέσων για το Kodi</summary>
        <description lang="el_GR">Το πρόσθετο AliveGR επιτρέπει την θέαση ροών με περιεχόμενο κυρίως εις την Ελληνική γλώσσα.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Ο δημιουργός του AliveGR δεν φιλοξενεί ή παρέχει οποιοδήποτε από τα απεικονιζόμενα πολυμέσα και περιεχόμένο εντός του μενού του και δεν μπορεί να θεωρηθεί υπεύθυνος για την ποιότητα ή την διαθεσιμότητα των ροών.
Το περιεχόμενο αναπαραγωγής κατά βούληση φιλτράρεται από διάφορες ιστοσελίδες ελεύθερα διαθέσιμες στο διαδίκτυο σε δημόσιους ιστότοπους. Το παρόν λογισμικό ενεργεί μόνο ως μηχανή αναζήτησης.
Παρακαλώ προσέξτε ότι το AliveGR δεν είναι επίσημο κομμάτι του Kodi αναπαραγωγέα πολυμέσων ή της καθορισμένης χρήσης του, είναι απλά μία μικροεφαρμογή που προστέθηκε στο σύστημά σας και που παρέχεται "όπως είναι" χωρίς εγγύηση.</disclaimer>
        <language>en el</language>
        <license>GNU GPL, version 2</license>
        <twitter>https://twitter.com/TwilightZer0</twitter>
        <forum>https://www.facebook.com/alivegr/</forum>
        <source>https://bitbucket.org/thgiliwt/plugin.video.alivegr</source>
        <website>https://alivegr.net/</website>
        <size>584908</size>
        <news>+ [B]1.31.X[/B] [COLOR green](04-07-2019)[/COLOR]
- Updated Ant1 live resolver as a new streamlink plugin
- Added resolver for startv official live stream as plugin for streamlink
- Tweaked ant1cy and omegacy plugins to return parent m3u8 urls with a plugin option as conditional
- Tweaked resolvers conditionals
- Updated welcome message, showing confluence skin for aeon nox, confluence and other similar skins
- Some cleanup on debug messages
- Use different method for new version detection
- Many other insignificant tweaks

=====================

[I]Past version:[/I]

+ [B]1.30.X[/B] [COLOR green](23-06-2019)[/COLOR]
- Tweaked openload plugin
- Updated generic streamlink plugin
- Added youtube-dl as optional dependency to augment generic plugin
- Disabled first time prompt temporarily
- Added setting to attempt to resolve dailymotion streams with resolveurl
- Removed ustream setting and resolving, it is now playable only via browser window
- Bump dependencies
- 3 years anniversary!!</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-1.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-2.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-3.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-4.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-5.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-6.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-7.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-8.jpg</screenshot>-->
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
