<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.AliveGR" name="AliveGR" version="1.4.1~beta4" provider-name="Thgiliwt">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="script.AliveGR.artwork" version="2.2.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.urlresolver" version="4.0.01"/>
        <import addon="script.module.streamlink.base" version="2017.09.06"/>
        <import addon="script.module.m3u8" version="0.2.10"/>
        <import addon="script.module.tulip" version="1.2.6"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="5.4.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="run.py">
        <provides>video audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en">AliveGR addon</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">AliveGR is an addon offering streaming content available in Greece. Please read disclaimer.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">AliveGR's author does not host, stream or distribute any of the content displayed inside this software and cannot be held responsible for the quality or availability of the listed streams.
    On demand content is scraped from various websites and are freely available on the internet. This software acts as indexer and not a linker.
    Kindly note that AliveGR is not an official part of the media player you are running, and therefore not to be mentioned within official support channels, this addon has nothing to do with the media player itself, nor it’s intended use, it is simply a third party plugin which has been added to your system and it is provided "as is".
        </disclaimer>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Πρόσθετο AliveGR</summary>
        <description lang="el_GR">Το πρόσθετο AliveGR προσφέρει ροές περιεχομένου διαθέσιμες στην Ελλάδα. Παρακαλώ διαβάστε την αποποίηση ευθυνών.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Ο δημιουργός του AliveGR δεν φιλοξενεί ή παρέχει οποιοδήποτε από τα απεικονιζόμενα πολυμέσα και περιεχόμένο εντός του μενού του και δεν μπορεί να θεωρηθεί υπεύθυνος για την ποιότητα ή την διαθεσιμότητα των ροών.
    Το περιεχόμενο αναπαραγωγής κατά βούληση φιλτράρεται από διάφορες ιστοσελίδες ελεύθερα διαθέσιμες στο διαδίκτυο. Το παρόν λογισμικό ενεργεί ως κατάλογος και όχι ως συνδεσμοποιητής.
    Παρακαλώ προσέξτε ότι το AliveGR δεν είναι επίσημο κομμάτι του Kodi αναπαραγωγέα πολυμέσων ή της καθορισμένης χρήσης του, είναι απλά μία μικροεφαρμογή plugin που προστέθηκε στο σύστημά σας και που παρέχεται "όπως είναι".
        </disclaimer>
        <language>en el</language>
        <license>GNU GPL, version 2</license>
        <website>https://twitter.com/TwilightZer0</website>
        <!--<forum></forum>-->
        <source>https://bitbucket.org/thgiliwt/plugin.video.alivegr</source>
        <size>661000</size>
        <news>
1.4.1 (14-09-2017)
- Passed Alpha CY's stream to alpha's resolver (it was direct in previous versions)
- Implemented for first run only, on every version bump:
  > View changelog
  > Reset indexers
  > Clear function cache
- Streamlink wrapper now returns None if it doesn't provide links
- Added yesno dialog for bookmarks purge function
- Added changelog for Greek language (post 1.4.0 versions)
- Sort methods are now called earlier (hopefully to fix methods on Krypton)

1.4.0 (11-09-2017)
- Added live music channels in music menu
- Tweaked music indexers
- Minor re-ordering of settings menu items
- Minor cosmetics here &amp; there
- Rebased dependencies
- Added optional custom plugin imports for streamlink wrapper
- Removed sort options from settings and now Kodi's native method is used (choice from sidebar)
- Added translated strings for live groups, instead of hardcoded
- Added translated strings for vod groups, taken from page and mapped to those strings
- Changed geoloc provider for ert's resolvers

1.3.4 (31-08-2017)
- More conditionals in player module to pass urls into streamlink's resolvers
- Added dialog for streamlink's resolver quality output (default is to pick best automatically)
- Tweaks in various indexers
- Removed youtube addon installation function (it gets installed as mandatory dependency)
- New repo source url

1.3.3 (29-08-2017)
- Fixed issues in episodes indexers
- Removed random picking of genre

1.3.2 (28-08-2017)
- Some more tweaks in player module for performance
- Rework of content switcher for main menu
  > it is now possible to switch off items individually
- Removed optional imports. They were not necessary to "import".
- Added source url in addon.xml

1.3.1 (27-08-2017)
- Minor bug fix for series play method on dialog picker

1.3.0 (27-08-2017)
- Minor rework in tools indexer
- Improved gm indexers
- Rework of player module to add caching and directory stream picker
- Removed radio stations, featured stations can be found in e-radio addon and radio menu from iptv simple client

1.2.6 (24-08-2017)
- Minor fix for gm_sports on demand indexer
- Added "musicvideos" parameter for music videos in respective section
- Aesthetic enhancements in music videos sections (albums, titles, artist infos)
- Fixed bug in VOD sub-indexers
- Various code cosmetics

1.2.5 (21-08-2017)
- Added yt_resolve setting for explicitly calling urlresolver for youtube streams
    > (when urlresolver is installed - defaults to true)
- Removed screenshots

1.2.4 (19-08-2017)
- Tweaked icon method call

1.2.3 (17-08-2017)
- Minor fix for iptv simple client integration on Kodi 17
- Minor code tweaks here &amp; there
- New internal resolver for ssh101 streams
- Updated &amp; tweaked disclaimer

1.2.2 (15-08-2017)
- Improved iptv simple client setup function by allowing installation of proxy module for streams' resolving
- Added actions item in settings menu directory
- Renamed root menu item from TV Guide to IPTV Simple Client
- Zouzounia Songs now installs zouzounia video plugin
- Various cosmetics

1.2.1 (11-08-2017)
- Quick fix in player module

1.2.0 (10-08-2017)
- New resolver for ustream via streamlink's resolvers
- Fixed Rytmos 949's top 20 indexer

1.1.2 (09-08-2017)
- New purge bookmarks action
- Delete settings folder action
- More rework in settings menu (new category maintenance &amp; fixes)
- Removed forgotten trailer import in music indexer (which caused indexer to fail)

1.1.1 (07-08-2017)
-Introduced reset indexers' methods action for manual operation
 > Before it was automatic and vod indexer was not saved

1.1.0 (04-08-2017)
- Minor aesthetic tweaks in music indexers
- Tweaked youtube setup api keys function (added yesno dialog for disabling wizard &amp; customizing for greek region)
- Added settings directory (old method still available via a setting)
- Added more channels for documentaries (set #2)

1.0.2 (27-07-2017)
- Minor tweak in music indexer and youtube_requests import method
- Moved radio item back to root menu
- Tweaked root indexer's filter for content type
- Deprecated changelog lines pre-1.0.0 versions (moved to "old")
- Re-ordered root menu items (search, bookmarks, music items on bottom)
- Tweaked message for disclaimer

1.0.1 (26-07-2017)
- Fix for live resolvers (Skai, Mega)
- Code tweaks
- First time prompt for disclaimer

1.0.0 (25-07-2017)
- New music menu
  > Two a-z indexes
  > Top 10 &amp; Top 20 Lists by Mad Greekz &amp; Rythmos 949's community
- Moved radio menu from root menu to music submenu
- Various code tweaks
Note: Anniversary update! 1 year old +
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-1.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-2.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-3.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-4.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-5.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-6.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-7.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-8.jpg</screenshot>-->
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
