<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.AliveGR" name="AliveGR" version="1.20" provider-name="Thgiliwt">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.alivegr.artwork" version="3.0.3"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.alivegr.logos" version="1.0.2"/>
        <!--<import addon="script.module.youtube.dl" version="17.709.0"/>-->
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.0.20"/>
        <import addon="script.module.streamlink.base" version="2018.12.05"/>
        <import addon="script.module.tulip" version="2.2.6"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.2.3"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="runner.py">
        <provides>video audio image executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">AliveGR addon</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">AliveGR is an addon offering streaming content available in Greece.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">AliveGR's author does not host, stream or distribute any of the content displayed inside this software and cannot be held responsible for the quality or availability of the listed streams.
On demand content is scraped from various websites and is freely available on the internet on public domains. This software acts only as a search engine.
Kindly note that AliveGR is not an official part of the media player you are running, and therefore not to be mentioned within official support channels, this addon has nothing to do with the media player itself, nor it’s intended use, it is simply a third party plugin which has been added to your system and it is provided "as is" with no warranty.
        </disclaimer>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Πρόσθετο AliveGR</summary>
        <description lang="el_GR">Το πρόσθετο AliveGR προσφέρει ροές περιεχομένου διαθέσιμες στην Ελλάδα.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Ο δημιουργός του AliveGR δεν φιλοξενεί ή παρέχει οποιοδήποτε από τα απεικονιζόμενα πολυμέσα και περιεχόμένο εντός του μενού του και δεν μπορεί να θεωρηθεί υπεύθυνος για την ποιότητα ή την διαθεσιμότητα των ροών.
Το περιεχόμενο αναπαραγωγής κατά βούληση φιλτράρεται από διάφορες ιστοσελίδες ελεύθερα διαθέσιμες στο διαδίκτυο σε δημόσιους ιστότοπους. Το παρόν λογισμικό ενεργεί μόνο ως μηχανή αναζήτησης.
Παρακαλώ προσέξτε ότι το AliveGR δεν είναι επίσημο κομμάτι του Kodi αναπαραγωγέα πολυμέσων ή της καθορισμένης χρήσης του, είναι απλά μία μικροεφαρμογή που προστέθηκε στο σύστημά σας και που παρέχεται "όπως είναι" χωρίς εγγύηση.
        </disclaimer>
        <language>en el</language>
        <license>GNU GPL, version 2</license>
        <website>https://twitter.com/TwilightZer0</website>
        <!--<forum></forum>-->
        <source>https://bitbucket.org/thgiliwt/plugin.video.alivegr</source>
        <size>523425</size>
        <news>[I][COLOR white]Welcome to A[/COLOR][COLOR blue]live[/COLOR][COLOR white]GR![/COLOR][/I]
[I][COLOR white]Television of the[/COLOR] [COLOR blue]greek[/COLOR] [COLOR red]generation[/COLOR][/I]

+ [B]1.20[/B] [COLOR green](13-01-2019)[/COLOR]
- Removed redundant youtube-resolver object conditional from its wrapper
- Zapping function now loads playlist into native mode by default, m3u kept as optional
- Create background progress dialod if length of directory items are equal or more than 50

============================================

[I]Past versions:[/I]

+ [B]1.19[/B] [COLOR yellow](10-01-2019)[/COLOR]
- Fix caching argument on live_tv function
- Changed method for inserting group switcher

+ [B]1.18[/B] [COLOR red](08-01-2019)[/COLOR]
- Some tweaks in music indexers to properly show artists when on music mode
- Various other tweaks

+ [B]1.17.X[/B] [COLOR red](29-12-2018)[/COLOR]
- Zapping mode gets a pre-resolve capability (defaults to off, enable from the settings menu)
- Added label processor to remove stupid comments from titles on techno picks indexer
- Re-included documentaries section (once labeled as Documentaries Set 1)

+ [B]1.16[/B] [COLOR red](25-12-2018)[/COLOR]
- Reuselanguageinvoker set to false. Behaviour on true does not respect settings changes, unfortunately.
- Added independent setting for live groups indexer reset
- Updated Mad TV's top 10 indexer (hybrid: spotify for metadata and youtube for video + thumbnails)
- Some other minor enhancements in music indexers</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-1.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-2.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-3.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-4.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-5.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-6.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-7.jpg</screenshot>-->
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-8.jpg</screenshot>-->
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
