<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.AliveGR" name="AliveGR" version="2.1.9" provider-name="Twilight0">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.alivegr.artwork" version="3.0.5"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.alivegr.logos" version="1.0.2"/>
<!--        <import addon="script.module.youtube.dl" version="18.619.0" optional="true"/>-->
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.0" optional="true"/>
        <import addon="script.module.streamlink.base" version="2020.03.05"/>
        <import addon="script.module.tulip" version="2.5.10"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.8.2"/>
        <import addon="script.module.pyxbmct" version="1.3.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video audio image executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">AliveGR addon for Kodi media center</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">AliveGR is an addon allowing streaming content available mostly in Greek language.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">AliveGR's author does not host, stream or distribute any of the content displayed inside this software and cannot be held responsible for the quality or availability of the listed streams.
On demand content is scraped from various websites and is freely available on the internet on public domains. This software acts only as a search engine.
Kindly note that AliveGR is not an official part of the media player you are running, and therefore not to be mentioned within official support channels, this addon has nothing to do with the media player itself, nor it’s intended use, it is simply a third party plugin which has been added to your system and it is provided "as is" with no warranty.</disclaimer>
        <summary lang="el_GR">AliveGR, Μικροεφαρμογή για το κέντρο πολυμέσων Kodi</summary>
        <description lang="el_GR">Το πρόσθετο AliveGR επιτρέπει την θέαση ροών με περιεχόμενο κυρίως εις την Ελληνική γλώσσα.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Ο δημιουργός του AliveGR δεν φιλοξενεί ή παρέχει οποιοδήποτε από τα απεικονιζόμενα πολυμέσα και περιεχόμένο εντός του μενού του και δεν μπορεί να θεωρηθεί υπεύθυνος για την ποιότητα ή την διαθεσιμότητα των ροών.
Το περιεχόμενο αναπαραγωγής κατά βούληση φιλτράρεται από διάφορες ιστοσελίδες ελεύθερα διαθέσιμες στο διαδίκτυο σε δημόσιους ιστότοπους. Το παρόν λογισμικό ενεργεί μόνο ως μηχανή αναζήτησης.
Παρακαλώ προσέξτε ότι το AliveGR δεν είναι επίσημο κομμάτι του αναπαραγωγέα πολυμέσων Kodi ή της καθορισμένης χρήσης του, είναι απλά μία μικροεφαρμογή που προστέθηκε στο σύστημά σας και που παρέχεται "όπως είναι" χωρίς καμία εγγύηση καλής λειτουργίας.</disclaimer>
        <language>en el</language>
        <license>GNU GPL, version 2</license>
        <forum>https://bitbucket.org/thgiliwt/plugin.video.alivegr/issues</forum>
        <source>https://bitbucket.org/thgiliwt/plugin.video.alivegr</source>
        <website>https://alivegr.net/</website>
        <size>584908</size>
        <news>+ [B]2.1.X[/B] [COLOR green]16-02-2020 -> 17-05-2020[/COLOR]
- Added pseudo-live youtube-based play items
- Inform user when unofficial streams are disabled
- Fixed youtube api keys setup wizard
- Disabled iptv setup action (will be re-enabled in a future release)
- Cartoon items can now be disabled from showing up on main indexers
- Tweaked streamlink plugins (ant1cy, skai, alphacy, ert, opentv)
- Live groups are now in fixed order instead of dynamic (makes channel ordering more predictable)


+ [B]2.0.X[/B] [COLOR red](30-01-2020 -> 10-02-2020)[/COLOR]
- Complete Python 3 support (Kodi ver.19+)
- Rework of several modules and functions
- Removed donation links from welcome message
- Re-added several menu items in kids section, including the addition of a new one
- Changed the way alternative/unofficial live/vod streams are enabled
- Removed openload streamlink plugin and accompanying settings
- Removed resolving capability on youtube externally
- Added several plugins for streamlink to resolve videos from official sources
- Added the ability to pin live channels
- Added a new menu item to view and send logs
- Added an option to pick a stream randomly
- Revamped search functionality
- Simplified some settings items
- Removed progress dialogs
- New random movie pick (50ies, 60ies, 70ies, 80ies, kids)
  > Ability to select from a random one or multiple ones as pseudo live playlist
- Several bug fixes</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <!--<screenshot>resources/alivegr-1.jpg</screenshot>-->
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
